<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>wibbly wobbly</title><link href="http://dharhas.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/misc.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://dharhas.github.io/</id><updated>2013-08-30T12:20:00-05:00</updated><entry><title>Trying Something New</title><link href="http://dharhas.github.io/blog/2013/08/30/trying-something-new/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-08-30T12:20:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Dharhas Pothina</name></author><id>tag:dharhas.github.io,2013-08-30:blog/2013/08/30/trying-something-new/</id><summary type="html">&lt;!-- PELICAN_BEGIN_SUMMARY --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At &lt;a href="http://conference.scipy.org/scipy2013/"&gt;SciPy2013&lt;/a&gt; I had lots of awesome 
conversations with folks. It was great to find that some of the things I'm
working on are actually of interest to a wider audience. One thing that came up 
again and again is whether I had blog posts describing some of my work (I didn't).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After seeing some really great examples of integrating the IPython notebook, github
and static website generators (which I had never heard of before), I decided that 
this looked like a blogging platform that might actually be something I could enjoy 
using. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway after several false starts, here is my attempt at a technical blog. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- PELICAN_END_SUMMARY --&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Inner Workings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sporadically over the laste few months since SciPy2013 I've tried various things found 
from googling blog and Ipython. After meandering down several twisty lanes, I've finally 
got something together that works (I think).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm basically using a python based static website generator &lt;a href="http://getpelican.com"&gt;Pelican&lt;/a&gt; 
along with the the liquid-tags plugin developed by &lt;a href="http://jakevdp.github.io/"&gt;Jave Vanderplas&lt;/a&gt;.
This website is basically a fork of his. I'm currently using the &lt;a href="https://github.com/duilio/pelican-octopress-theme"&gt;octopress-pelican&lt;/a&gt;
theme but will probably tweak it over time. In my next post I'll try a blogging a simple 
IPython notebook to see if I have all the kinks worked out.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="kicking-the-tires"></category></entry></feed>